A Guide to the Hao Wang papers, Rockefeller University Faculty FA274
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Manuscripts, Notes, and Notebooks, 3
  - DGW2 - "Computation and the Axiomatic Method" (Box 59, Folder 1031)
  - DGW-3, 3/1992, Chapter 3, "Some Problems about Algorithmism and Physicalism" (Box 60, Folder 1032)
  - DGW3 (1992), MGW, Chapter 3, "On Algorithmism and Physicalism: Can Machines Think?" (Box 60, Folder 1033)
  - Dialectics, 1973-1977 (Box 60, Folder 1034)
  - "Dialectics and Natural Science" by Hao Wang (Box 60, Folder 1035)
  - "The Disappearance of Time: An Essay on the Philosophy of Kurt Gödel" and other materials by Palle Yourgrau (Box 60, Folder 1036)
  - "The Disappearance of Time: Kurt Gödel and the Idealistic Tradition in Philosophy" by Palle Yourgrau (Box 61, Folder 1037)
  - Discarded Drafts, 1954-1956 (Box 61, Folder 1038)
  - Discussions with Gödel, 1971-1976 (Box 61, Folder 1039)
  - Distribution List, "The Pursuit of Purity" (Box 61, Folder 1040)
  - "Does V Equal L?" by Penelope Maddy (Box 61, Folder 1041)
  - "Dominoes and the AEA Case of the Decision Problem" (Box 61, Folder 1042)
  - B. Dunham, "Theorem Testing by Computer" (Box 61, Folder 1043)
  - Ronald Dworkin, "Law's Empire" (Box 61, Folder 1044)
  - “Early Wittgenstein (W1) and the 'Tractatus'” (Box 61, Folder 1045)
  - “Eine einfache Methode zur Bestimmung der Unlösbarkeitsgrade von Entscheidungsproblemen Kombinatorischer Systeme” by Egon Börger (Box 61, Folder 1046)
  - "Einstein and Gödel: Contrast and Friendship" (Box 61, Folder 1047)
  - El. Philos. of Math., 1955-1956 (Box 61, Folder 1048)
  - Elementary Philosophy of Mathematics, 1955-1956 (Box 62, Folder 1049)
  - Elgot, C.C., "Decision Problems of Finite Automata" and "The Löwenheim-Skolem Theorem” by R.L. Vaught (Box 62, Folder 1050)
  - English Version of Two Papers Published in French, "Cantor and Naïve Set Theory" (Box 62, Folder 1051)
  - [Envelope Label in Chinese] (Box 62, Folder 1052)
  - Anthony Everett (Box 62, Folder 1053)
  - "Every Schoolchild Knows," edited by Brockman and Matson (Box 62, Folder 1054)
  - Extra Copy of CG4, Gödel-related (Box 62, Folder 1055)
  - FCG1, Chapter 7, 5/1994, "A Logical Journey: From Gödel to Philosophy" (Box 62, Folder 1056)
  - FCG3, 12/1993, Chapter 3, "The Gap between Wish and Fact," "A Logical Journey: From Gödel to Philosophy" (Box 62, Folder 1057)
  - FCG(3), SWF, 1993, Gödel-related (Box 62, Folder 1058)
  - FCG4, 12/1993, Chapter 4, "The Conversations and Their Background," "A Logical Journey: From Gödel to Philosophy" (Box 62, Folder 1059)
  - FCG4, Chapter 4, "The Conversations and Their Background," from "A Logical Journey: From Gödel to Philosophy" (Box 63, Folder 1060)
  - FCG, Chapter 5, "Philosophies and Philosophers," "A Logical Journey: From Gödel to Philosophy" (Box 63, Folder 1061)
  - FCG5, Chapter 5, "Philosophies and Philosophers," from "A Logical Journey: From Gödel to Philosophy" (Box 63, Folder 1062)
  - FCG6, Chapter 6, "Minds and Machines," "A Logical Journey: From Gödel to Philosophy" (Box 63, Folder 1063)
  - FCG6, Chapter 6, "Minds and Machines: On Computerism and Physicalism," from "A Logical Journey: From Gödel to Philosophy" (Box 63, Folder 1064)
  - FCG7, Chapter 7, "Platonism or Objectivism," "A Logical Journey: From Gödel to Philosophy" (Box 63, Folder 1065)
  - FCG8, 3/1994, Chapter 8, "Set Theory and Logic as Concept Theory," "A Logical Journey: From Gödel to Philosophy" (Box 63, Folder 1066)
  - FCG8, Gödel-related (Box 63, Folder 1067)
  - FCG9, 3/1994, Chapter 9, "Gödel's Conception of Philosophy," "A Logical Journey: From Gödel to Philosophy" (Box 63, Folder 1068)
  - FCG9, Gödel-related (Box 64, Folder 1069)
  - FCGE, 4/1994, "A Logical Journey: From Gödel to Philosophy" (Box 64, Folder 1070)
  - FCGH, "A Logical Journey: From Gödel to Philosophy" (Box 64, Folder 1071)
  - FCGH, 4/1994, "Preface, Intro...," "A Logical Journey: From Gödel to Philosophy" (Box 64, Folder 1072)
  - FCGT, FCGE, Gödel-related (Box 64, Folder 1073)
  - Solomon Feferman, Includes: “Why a Little Bit Goes a Long Way: Logical Foundations of Scientifically Applicable Mathematics” by Solomon Feferman “What Rests on What? The Proof-Theoretic Analysis of Mathematics” by Solomon Feferman “Weyl Vindicated: ‘Das Kontinuum’ 70 Years Later” by Solomon Feferman “The Development of Programs for the Foundation of Mathematics in the First Third of the 20th Century” by Solomon Feferman “Predicative Foundations of Arithmetic” by Solomon Feferman and Geoffrey Hellman (Box 64, Folder 1074)
  - FHLG, Introduction, Gödel-related (Box 64, Folder 1075)
  - Final Solutions: God and Afterlife, Includes: “New Directions in Science and in Society: From Traditions to Innovations” “China and Western Philosophy” [in Chinese] “Concerning the Materialist Didactic” “The Gap between Wish and Fact” (Box 64, Folder 1076)
  - "Finite Mathematics" by Shaughan Lavine (Box 64, Folder 1077)
  - "Finitism" by W.W. Tait (Box 64, Folder 1078)
  - FMR - Final - "Mathematical Realism" (Box 65, Folder 1079)
  - "For Perspicuous Objectivity: Discussions between Gödel and Wittgenstein" (Box 65, Folder 1080)
  - "For Perspicuous Objectivity: Discussions between Gödel and Wittgenstein" (Box 65, Folder 1081)
  - "For Perspicuous Objectivity: Discussions with Gödel and Wittgenstein" (Box 65, Folder 1082)
  - Forcing, 1965 (Notes), Includes: “Notes in Set Theory,” October 12, 1967 (Box 65, Folder 1083)
  - "The Formal and the Intuitive" (Box 65, Folder 1084)
  - "The Formal and the Intuitive in the Biological Sciences" (Box 66, Folder 1085)
  - "The Formal and the Intuitive in the Biological Sciences" (Box 66, Folder 1086)
  - "The Formal and the Intuitive in the Biological Sciences" NYU [New York University] Talk (Box 66, Folder 1087)
  - Fragment on Philosophy and Mathematics (Box 66, Folder 1088)
  - Freud and M.C., 1982; Includes: “The World for a Self: Descartes and Freud” “Freedom of the Will and the Concept of a Person” by Harry G. Frankfurt “A Response to Otto Kernberg’s ‘The Dynamic Unconscious and the Self’” by Marcia Cavell Aufhauser “Self-Reflection, Other Minds, and the Grounds of Dialogue” “Speaking in the First Person” “Mental Structure and Self-Consciousness” by Brian O’Shaughnessy “Matter, Mind and Models” by Marvin Minsky “Self-Consciousness, A Critical Introduction to a Theory” by Dieter Henrich “Central Dialogue” by Marcia Cavell “Taste and the Moral Sense” by Marcia Cavell “The Guilt of Oedipus” by Marcia Cavell Aufhauser “Guilt and Guilt Feeling: Power and the Limits of Power” by Marcia Cavell Aufhauser “Understanding Others” “Self-Consciousness” (Box 66, Folder 1089)
  - "From Alternative Philosophies to Husserl" (Box 66, Folder 1090)
  - "From Mathematics to Philosophy" (Box 67, Folder 1091)
  - From Mathematics to Philosophy (Full Xerox) (Box 67, Folder 1092)
  - "From Mathematics to Philosophy," Table of Contents" (Box 67, Folder 1093)
  - FTP 1990, "To and From Philosophy: Discussions with Gödel and Wittgenstein" (Box 67, Folder 1094)
  - General History of Formal Logic (Box 67, Folder 1095)
  - Gerhard Gentzen (Box 67, Folder 1096)
  - Norman Geschwind (Box 68, Folder 1097)
  - The Gibbs Lecture (Box 68, Folder 1098)
  - Gödel, A (Box 68, Folder 1099)
  - Gödel, Abbreviations and References (Box 68, Folder 1100)
  - Gödel and the Institute for Advanced Study (Box 68, Folder 1101)
  - "Gödel and Wittgenstein" (Box 68, Folder 1102)
  - Gödel and Wittgenstein (Box 68, Folder 1103)
  - Gödel - Aristotle Conference (Box 69, Folder 1104)
  - Gödel - Bernays (Box 69, Folder 1105)
  - Gödel Bibliography - Hao Wang (Box 69, Folder 1106)
  - Gödel-Briefe, 1-67d, 1945-1950, 1 (Box 69, Folder 1107)
  - Gödel-Briefe, 68-119d, 1951-1955, 2 (Box 69, Folder 1108)
  - Gödel-Briefe, 120-168d, 1956-1960, 3 (Box 69, Folder 1109)
  - Gödel-Briefe, 169-237a and 238-244, 1964-1965, 1966, 4 (Box 69, Folder 1110)
  - Gödel, Chapter 1 (Box 70, Folder 1111)
  - Gödel, Chapter 1, "A Life of Fundamental Theoretical Work" (Box 70, Folder 1112)
  - Gödel, Chapter 2 (Box 70, Folder 1113)
  - Gödel, Chapter 2, "Gödel and Philosophy" (Box 70, Folder 1114)
  - Gödel, Chapter 3 (Box 70, Folder 1115)
  - Gödel, Chapter 3, "The Conceptual in Science and Technology" (Box 70, Folder 1116)
  - Gödel, Chapter 4 (Box 70, Folder 1117)
  - Gödel, Chapter 4, "Auseinandersetzungen" (Box 70, Folder 1118)
  - Gödel, Chapter 5 (Box 70, Folder 1119)
  - Gödel, Chapter 6 (Box 70, Folder 1120)
  - Gödel, Chapter 6, "Some Facts about Kurt Gödel" (Box 70, Folder 1121)
  - Gödel, Chapter 6, 7, and 8 (Box 70, Folder 1122)
  - Gödel, Chapter 7 (Box 71, Folder 1123)
  - Gödel, Chapter 8 (Box 71, Folder 1124)
  - Gödel, Chapter 9 (Box 71, Folder 1125)
  - Gödel, Chapter 10 (Box 71, Folder 1126)
  - Gödel, Chapters 9 and 10, "The Nachlass" and "Published Thoughts and Delivered Lectures" (Box 71, Folder 1127)
  - Gödel, Chapters 9, 10, Part C, Chapter 11, Includes: “The Nachlass” “Published Thoughts and Delivered Lectures” “Conversations” “October 1971 to February 1972” (Box 71, Folder 1128)
  - Gödel, Chapter 11, "October 1971 to February 1972" (Box 71, Folder 1129)
  - Gödel, Chapters 12, 13, 14, Part D, and Chapter 15, Includes: “March to December 1972” “October 1975 to January 1976” “February to June 1976” “Texts” “Mathematical Papers (Box 71, Folder 1130)
  - Gödel, Chapter 13, "October 1975 to January 1976" (Box 72, Folder 1131)
  - Gödel, Chapters 16, 17, and 18, Includes: “Philosophical Papers” “Fragments Related to the Conversations” “Large Sets” (Box 72, Folder 1132)
  - Gödel, Chapter L, "Kurt Gödel, A Life of the Mind (a sketch)" (Box 72, Folder 1133)
  - Gödel, Chapter M, "Mind, Matter, Concept" (Box 72, Folder 1134)
  - Gödel, Chronology (1 of 2) (Box 72, Folder 1135)
  - Gödel, Chronology (1 of 2) (Box 72, Folder 1136)
  - Gödel, Anthony Everett (Box 72, Folder 1137)
  - Gödel, "Fragments of a Framework" (Box 72, Folder 1138)
  - Gödel - Gibbs Lecture, 1951 (Box 73, Folder 1139)
  - Gödel - H.Wang - Notes, October 13, 1971 to January 19, 1972 (Box 73, Folder 1140)
  - Gödel, Hao Wang's Talk at Queens College, March 1, 1979 (Box 73, Folder 1141)
  - Gödel, Head (Box 73, Folder 1142)
  - Gödel, Honorary Degree, Rockefeller University (Box 73, Folder 1143)
  - Gödel, Index (Box 73, Folder 1144)
  - Gödel - Kleene, May-July 1977 (Box 73, Folder 1145)
  - Gödel Letters, 1967-1968 (Box 73, Folder 1146)
  - Gödel - McGraw-Hill, "Modern Scientists and Engineers" (Box 73, Folder 1147)
  - "Gödel, Marx, Wittgenstein" (Box 73, Folder 1148)
  - Gödel - Menger Colloquium (Box 73, Folder 1149)
  - Gödel, Mind, Matter, Machine, and Mathematics - HW (Box 73, Folder 1150)
  - Gödel - Miscellaneous (Box 73, Folder 1151)
  - Gödel, "On Rationalistic Optimism" (Box 73, Folder 1152)
  - Gödel, "Part A" (1 of 2) (Box 74, Folder 1153)
  - Gödel, "Part A" (2 of 2) (Box 74, Folder 1154)
  - Gödel - "Part A," "Discussions with Kurt Gödel" and "Reflections on Kurt Gödel," Royalty Statements (Box 74, Folder 1155)
  - Gödel, "Part B" (1 of 2) (Box 74, Folder 1156)
  - Gödel, "Part B" (2 of 2) (Box 74, Folder 1157)
  - Gödel, "Part C" (1 of 2) (Box 75, Folder 1158)
  - Gödel, "Part C" (2 of 2) (Box 75, Folder 1159)
  - Gödel, Part D, Introduction, Chapters 15 and 16 (Box 75, Folder 1160)
  - Gödel - Quine Memoir (Box 75, Folder 1161)
  - Gödel-related Manuscripts, Includes: “Philosophical Reflections on Gödel’s Cosmology” by Palle Yourgrau “Some Observations about the Relationship between Theory of Relativity and Kantian Philosophy” by Kurt Gödel “Gödel’s Universe” by H.W. Rupertsberger “Das Gödel-Universum und die Philosophie der Zeit” by Andreas Bartels “To and From Philosophy – Discussions with Gödel and Wittgenstein” “Philosophy through Mathematics and Logic” (Box 75, Folder 1162)
  - Gödel - Reviews and Bibliography (Box 75, Folder 1163)
  - "Gödel the Philosopher" (Box 75, Folder 1164)
  - "Gödel's Mental Development" for "Bulletin of Symbolic Logic" (Box 75, Folder 1165)
  - Gödel's Nachlass (Box 76, Folder 1166)
  - "Gödel's and Some Other Examples of Problem Transmutation" (Box 76, Folder 1167)
  - Gödel's and Some Other Examples of Problem Transmutation (Box 76, Folder 1168)
  - Gödel's Thesis (Box 76, Folder 1169)
  - Grandjean Questionnaire (Box 76, Folder 1170)
  - Branko Grünbaum (Box 76, Folder 1171)
  - Richard Halpern, "On Why Mathematical Proofs are Surprising" (Box 76, Folder 1172)
  - W. Hanf (Box 76, Folder 1173)
  - Harvard Lecture Notes, Fall, 1946 (Box 76, Folder 1174)
  - Harvard Notes and Teaching Materials (Box 76, Folder 1175)
  - Harvard University, Applied Mathematics 234 (Box 76, Folder 1176)
  - Crispin Hasler (Box 76, Folder 1177)
  - "Heautonomy: Kant on Reflective Judgment and Systematicity" by Juliet Floyd (Box 76, Folder 1178)
  - Jacques Herbrand (Box 76, Folder 1179)
  - "Herbrand Theory and Group Theory," To Reduce the Decision Problem to the Solution of Certain Equations (Box 76, Folder 1180)
  - Richard J. Herrnstein (Box 76, Folder 1181)
  - Hilbert Tenth Problem (Box 76, Folder 1182)
  - David Hilbert, "On the Infinite" (Box 77, Folder 1183)
  - "Hilbert's Axiomatic Method and the Laws of Thought" by Michael Hallett (Box 77, Folder 1184)
  - "History of the Gödel Family" by Rudolf Gödel (Box 77, Folder 1185)
  - Wells Hively, "Specifying 'Terminal Behavior' in Mathematics" (Box 77, Folder 1186)
  - Kai Hong Dissertation (Box 77, Folder 1187)
  - William M. Honig (Box 77, Folder 1188)
  - Shih-Hua Hu (Box 77, Folder 1189)
  - IDGW, 1991, "Imagined Discussions with Gödel and with Wittgenstein", Includes: “Kripke on Wittgenstein on Rules” by Warren Goldfarb “I Want You to Bring Me a Slab: Remarks on the Opening Sections of the Philosophical Investigations” by Warren D. Goldfarb “Wittgenstein on Understanding” by Warren Goldfarb (Box 77, Folder 1190)
  - IDGW (Kirchberg - 1991), ("Imagined Discussions with Gödel and with Wittgenstein") (Box 77, Folder 1191)
  - "Imagined Discussions with Gödel and with Wittgenstein" (Box 77, Folder 1192)
  - Indices of Diskette Contents (1 of 3) (Box 77, Folder 1193)
  - Indices of Diskette Contents (2 of 3) (Box 78, Folder 1194)
  - Indices of Diskette Contents (3 of 3) (Box 78, Folder 1195)
  - Induction, Philosophy of Science, 1950s (Box 78, Folder 1196)
  - Inductive Sets, 1957-1958; Includes: “Further Notes on Arithmetic Models” by G. Kreisel and Hao Wang “W and O” (Box 78, Folder 1197)
  - Introduction (Clean Copy), "From Mathematics to Philosophy" (Box 78, Folder 1198)
  - Introduction, "From Mathematics to Philosophy" (Box 78, Folder 1199)
  - Introduction, "From Mathematics to Philosophy" (Box 79, Folder 1200)
  - Introduction (Miscellaneous Rejected), "From Mathematics to Philosophy" (Box 79, Folder 1201)
  - "Introduction to the Second Edition" and portions of CG1 and CG2 (Box 79, Folder 1202)
  - "Introduction to the Second Edition," "From Mathematics to Philosophy" (Box 79, Folder 1203)
  - Insulin (Box 79, Folder 1204)
  - "Is it Possible to Construct a Perception Machine?" by Gerald M. Edelman and George N. Reeke, Jr. (Box 79, Folder 1205)
  - "Is Mathematics Syntax of Language?" by Kurt Gödel (Box 79, Folder 1206)
  - "Is the Human Mind a Turing Machine?" by David King (Box 79, Folder 1207)
  - Andrew S. Kahr (Box 79, Folder 1208)
  - Kahr Thesis, "A Minimal Reduction Class for the Entscheidungsproblem" by Andrew Seth Kahr, 1960 (Box 79, Folder 1209)
  - Kang Hong-kuei's Chinese Translation of RG (Box 79, Folder 1210)
  - Kant and Einstein Plus Philosophical Viewpoint, Gödel-related (Box 79, Folder 1211)
  - Ng Tai Kee (Box 80, Folder 1212)
  - Kirchberg, 1989, "To Will Only Perpsicuity" (Box 80, Folder 1213)
  - S.C. Kleene (Box 80, Folder 1214)
  - "Knowledge" (Box 80, Folder 1215)
  - Simon Kochen, "The Interpretation of Quantum Mechanices" and "Ultraproducts in the Theory of Models" (Box 80, Folder 1216)
  - Gerhard G. Kohlmayr (Box 80, Folder 1217)
  - A.N. Kolmogorov (Box 80, Folder 1218)
  - D. König, “Über eine Schlussweise aus dem Endlichen ins Unendliche” (Box 80, Folder 1219)
  - D.L. Kreider, "Constructive Versions of Ordinal Number Classes" (Box 80, Folder 1220)
  - Kreisel (Box 80, Folder 1221)
  - G. Kreisel (Box 80, Folder 1222)
  - Saul A. Kripke (Box 81, Folder 1223)
  - Kurt Gödel, “Conversations” (Box 81, Folder 1224)
  - Kurt Gödel Gesellschaft Contribution, “Mind Brain Machine” (Box 81, Folder 1225)
  - Kurt Gödel, Introductory Note: The Completeness of the Axioms of the Functional Calculus of Logic (Box 81, Folder 1226)
  - "Kurt Gödel's Intellectual Development" (Box 81, Folder 1227)
  - "Kurt Gödel's Intellectual Development" (Box 81, Folder 1228)
  - "Large Sets", Includes: “Set Existence Principles of Schoenfield, Ackermann, and Powell” by W.N. Reinhardt (Box 81, Folder 1229)
  - "Large Sets," Preliminary Draft (Box 81, Folder 1230)
  - LCG, 10/1991, ChapL - "Preface, Introduction," "A Logical Journey: From Gödel to Philosophy" (Box 81, Folder 1231)
  - LCG, Gödel-related (Box 81, Folder 1232)
  - Lecture Notes and Manuscripts, 1965-1966 (Box 82, Folder 1233)
  - Lecture Notes from Course on American Imperialism (Box 82, Folder 1234)
  - T.D. Lee, 1980s (Box 82, Folder 1235)
  - "Letters to a Student of Philosophy" by M. Drury (Box 82, Folder 1236)
  - Life and Letters, Gödel-related (Box 82, Folder 1237)
  - Beng-Qiu Lin (Box 82, Folder 1238)
  - "Logic and Axiomatic Set Theory" by Paul Cohen (Box 82, Folder 1239)
  - "Logic and Computers" (1 of 2) (Box 83, Folder 1240)
  - "Logic and Computers" (2 of 2) (Box 83, Folder 1241)
  - Logic and Computers (Box 83, Folder 1242)
  - "Logic and Computers: A Collection of Essays" (Box 83, Folder 1243)
  - "Logic and Computers: A Collection of Essays" (Box 83, Folder 1244)
  - "Logic and Foundations", October 1966 (Box 83, Folder 1245)
  - "Logic and Foundations" Lecture, October 17, 1966 (Box 83, Folder 1246)
  - "Logic and Foundations: Formalization of Mathematical Concepts" (Box 83, Folder 1247)
  - "Logic and Materialism" (Box 83, Folder 1248)
  - "Logic and Materialism" (Box 83, Folder 1249)
  - "Logic and Social Praxis" and "China and Transitional Phases after Revolution" (Box 83, Folder 1250)
  - "Logic and Truth" (Box 83, Folder 1251)
  - "Logic as the Theory of Concepts" (Box 83, Folder 1252)
  - "Logic of Entailment" by Bang-Jin Ling, Qi-Jin Pu, and Jun-Bi Zou (Box 83, Folder 1253)
  - "A Logical Journey: From Gödel to Philosophy," Chapter 0 (Box 84, Folder 1254)
  - "A Logical Journey: From Gödel to Philosophy," Chapter 0 (Box 84, Folder 1255)
  - "A Logical Journey: From Gödel to Philosophy," Chapters 0, 1, and 3 (Box 84, Folder 1256)
  - "A Logical Journey: From Gödel to Philosophy," Chapter 1 (Box 84, Folder 1257)
  - "A Logical Journey: From Gödel to Philosophy," Chapter 1 (Box 84, Folder 1258)
  - "A Logical Journey: From Gödel to Philosophy," Chapter 2 (Box 84, Folder 1259)
  - "A Logical Journey: From Gödel to Philosophy," Chapter 2 (Box 84, Folder 1260)
  - "A Logical Journey: From Gödel to Philosophy," Chapter 3 (Box 84, Folder 1261)
  - "A Logical Journey: From Gödel to Philosophy," Chapter 3 (Box 84, Folder 1262)
  - "A Logical Journey: From Gödel to Philosophy," Chapters 3, 4, and 5 (Box 84, Folder 1263)
  - "A Logical Journey: From Gödel to Philosophy," Chapter 4 (Box 85, Folder 1264)
  - "A Logical Journey: From Gödel to Philosophy," Chapter 4 (Box 85, Folder 1265)
  - "A Logical Journey: From Gödel to Philosophy," Chapter 5 (Box 85, Folder 1266)
  - "A Logical Journey: From Gödel to Philosophy," Chapter 5 (Box 85, Folder 1267)
  - "A Logical Journey: From Gödel to Philosophy," Chapter 6 (Box 85, Folder 1268)
  - "A Logical Journey: From Gödel to Philosophy," Chapter 6 (Box 85, Folder 1269)
  - "A Logical Journey: From Gödel to Philosophy," Chapters 6, 7, and 8 (Box 85, Folder 1270)
  - "A Logical Journey: From Gödel to Philosophy," Chapter 7 (Box 85, Folder 1271)
  - "A Logical Journey: From Gödel to Philosophy," Chapter 7 (Box 85, Folder 1272)
  - "A Logical Journey: From Gödel to Philosophy," Chapter 8 (Box 85, Folder 1273)
  - "A Logical Journey: From Gödel to Philosophy," Chapter 8 (Box 85, Folder 1274)
  - "A Logical Journey: From Gödel to Philosophy," Chapter 9 (Box 85, Folder 1275)
  - "A Logical Journey: From Gödel to Philosophy," Chapter 9 (Box 85, Folder 1276)
  - "A Logical Journey: From Gödel to Philosophy," Chapters 9, 10, and References (Box 86, Folder 1277)
  - "A Logical Journey: From Gödel to Philosophy," Chapter 10 (Box 86, Folder 1278)
  - "A Logical Journey: From Gödel to Philosophy," Chapter 10 (Box 86, Folder 1279)
  - "A Logical Journey: From Gödel to Philosophy," Chapter 11 (Box 86, Folder 1280)
  - "A Logical Journey: From Gödel to Philosophy," Chapter 11 (Box 86, Folder 1281)
  - "A Logical Journey: From Gödel to Philosophy," (Correspondence, etc.) (Box 86, Folder 1282)
  - "A Logical Journey: From Gödel to Philosophy," Current (Box 86, Folder 1283)
  - "A Logical Journey: From Gödel to Philosophy," Table of Contents (Box 86, Folder 1284)
  - Logical Truth, Chapter IV from "From Mathematics to Philosophy" (Box 86, Folder 1285)
  - John McCarthy (Box 86, Folder 1286)
  - Machines as Aid to Discovery, 1953-1954 (Box 86, Folder 1287)
  - "Machines, Recursions, Algorithms, and Productions" (Box 86, Folder 1288)
  - Robert McNaughton (Box 86, Folder 1289)
  - Penelope Maddy (Box 86, Folder 1290)
  - Mailing List and Acknowledgements, "Reflections on Kurt Gödel" (Box 87, Folder 1291)
  - Main Control, 1992 (Box 87, Folder 1292)
  - “A Mansion of Many Rooms,” CG2 (→CGF1), Gödel-related, Includes: “Work as Part of Gödel’s Life" (Box 87, Folder 1293)
  - Manuscript, "After Mathematics/Mathematical Concepts" (Box 87, Folder 1294)
  - Manuscript, "2PM," "For Perspicuous Objectivity: Discussions with Gödel and Wittgenstein" (Box 87, Folder 1295)
  - Manuscript by A.P. Hazen (Box 87, Folder 1296)
  - Manuscript, From Mathematics to Philosophy (Box 88, Folder 1297)
  - Manuscript, From Mathematics to Philosophy, Chapter II, "Characterization of General Mathematical Concepts" (Box 88, Folder 1298)
  - Manuscript, Chapter VI from "From Mathematics to Philosophy" (Box 88, Folder 1299)
  - Manuscript, From Mathematics to Philosophy, Chapter XII, "Themes and Approaches" (Box 88, Folder 1300)
  - Manuscript, Locke Lectures (Box 88, Folder 1301)
  - Manuscript, "Logical Truth," Chapter IV from "From Mathematics to Philosophy," Reject (Box 88, Folder 1302)
  - Manuscript, "Mathematical Arguments on Minds and Machines," Revised (Box 88, Folder 1303)
  - Manuscript, "Skolem and Gödel", 1993-1994 (Box 88, Folder 1304)
  - Manuscripts and Referee Reports (Box 88, Folder 1305)
  - Manuscripts, Gödel-related (Box 88, Folder 1306)
  - Manuscripts, "Logic and Purity of Mind: Wittgenstein, Gödel, and Ideals of Philosophy" and "Purity of Mind: Philosophy through Gödel and Wittgenstein" (Box 88, Folder 1307)
  - Manuscripts, "Men and Machines" (Box 88, Folder 1308)
  - Manuscripts and Notes [Folder title in Chinese], 1940s (Box 89, Folder 1309)
  - Manuscripts and Notes, 1948-1949 (Box 89, Folder 1310)
  - Manuscripts and Notes, 1951 (Box 89, Folder 1311)
  - Manuscripts and Notes, 1953-1954 (Box 89, Folder 1312)
  - Manuscripts and Notes, 1966-1970 (Box 89, Folder 1313)
  - Manuscripts for "Popular Lectures", 1978 (Box 89, Folder 1314)
  - Mathieu Marion (Box 90, Folder 1315)
  - "Marx and Wittgenstein" (Box 90, Folder 1316)
  - Material for Gödel Book?, Includes: “The Formal and the Intuitive in the Biological Sciences” “Computer Theorem Proving and Artificial Intelligence” “Aperiodicity and Constraints” “Gödel and Einstein as Companions” “Can Minds do More than Brains?” “Gödel’s and Some Other Examples of Problem Transmutation” (Box 90, Folder 1317)
  - Materialist Dialectic, 1974-1975 (Box 90, Folder 1318)
  - "Mathematical Realism - A Zone of Convergence", 1988-1989 (Box 90, Folder 1319)